(tranquil ambient music)
- Hey friends,
welcome back to the channel.
If you're new here, my name is Ali,
and I'm a doctor based in the UK.
And in this video,
we're talking about a topic
very close to my heart,
which is how to type faster.
Now having a ridiculously
fast typing speed
is one of my superpowers in life.
And I think anyone can become
at least twice as productive
if you just improve your typing speed.
And so in this video, we're gonna talk
about the benefits of
improving your typing speed.
And then I'm gonna go over
eight actionable practical tips
on how you can personally
improve your typing speed
so that you can become a
productivity grease monkey.